virginmegastore.me 2017-02-23

# Website Privacy Policy | Virgin Megastore

## VIRGIN MEGASTORE - WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY

This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) sets out the basis on which Virgin Megastore (“Virgin”, “we”, “our”, etc.) collects, uses and discloses personal information obtained from you when using www.virginmegastore.ae (the “Website”). References in this Policy to “Virgin Megastore Group” are references to different legal entities related by way of common corporate history, and typically trading under the VIRGIN MEGASTORE brand in the United Arab Emirates. This Policy is effective from 01.01.2016.

By visiting the Website, and/or by using any services provided via this Website, you expressly agree to be bound by the terms of this Policy and you consent to our collection, use and disclosure of your information in accordance with the terms of this Policy. We may amend this Policy at any time without notice, and such amendments become effective from the date upon which we make them available on the Website. If you do not agree to the Policy (including any amendments), then you should immediately cease using the Website.

YOUR INFORMATION

 The type of information we collect from you is either personal to you, or is general in nature:

• Personal Information: When you register on the Website as a customer, update your information, purchase any goods or services, take part in promotions or send emails to us, you provide us with information that we store and process. Such information may include your name, address, phone number, email address, purchase and transaction history, billing information, interests, and other such 'Personal Information'. 

• General Information: We also receive more general information from you as a result of your visits to, and use of, the Website. This general information does not identify you personally, and can include information such as your IP address, the date and time you access the Website, length of time you spend on the Website, your browsing history (recorded by the text and graphics files that compose that page), the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our Website, and other such 'General Information'.

COLLECTING AND USING INFORMATION

Most of this Website can be used without giving us any information. However, certain services may involve collection of information from you. We use this information to provide you with a better service, and in particular to: keep internal records; improve our products, services and this Website; communicate with you if you have ordered or purchased products from us; contact you for market research purposes; and provide you with information about new products, promotions, special offers and other information.

We use Personal Information for a range of business-related purposes, including: account registration (eg. your name, telephone number and email address); billing information, transaction and credit card information (should you make a purchase with us); and information regarding your interests, demographics, experiences and contact preferences in order to provide you with further correspondence about our products and services. If you contact us via the Website, or via email to the contacts set out on the Website, we may keep a record of that correspondence.

We use General Information to help us make the Website more useful to visitors (including to help us assess content of interest to visitors), and for other purposes such as determining the Website’s technical design specifications and identifying system performance or problem areas, for tracking activity on the Website, preparing reports, assessing trends, and otherwise monitoring the way in which the Website is being used – none of which would be in a way that personally identifies any users.

NON-DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

You agree that we may share your Personal Information within the Virgin Megastore Group and with any subcontractors that are assisting us with the operation of the Website and who have agreed to abide by the terms of this policy. We will not share, sell or rent your Personal Information in any manner to any third parties outside the Virgin Megastore Group and those subcontractors, except when we have your permission; or if required to do so by law or any governing authority; or to protect our own legitimate interests.

SECURITY

Keeping your Personal Information secure and preventing unauthorized access is of utmost priority to us, and we take all steps reasonably necessary to protect your Personal Information against any unauthorized access, use, alteration, disclosure or destruction. Whilst we have put in place physical, electronic and managerial procedures to secure and safeguard your Personal Information, we will not be held responsible for any unauthorized access by third parties and we cannot guarantee that the Personal Information provided by you or that is transmitted via this Website or by e-mail is totally secure and safe.

COOKIES

The Website uses cookies, which are files that store information on your hard drive that allow a website to recognize users, track new users and to record session information. Most browsers are automatically set to accept cookies but if you choose you can disable the cookies from your browser.

LINKS TO THIRD PARTY WEBSITES 

The Website may provide links to other third party websites not within our control. We cannot be responsible or liable for the content of such websites and we advise you to exercise caution and review and understand the privacy policy of such websites before submitting any of your Personal Information to them. 

APPLICABLE LAW AND JURISDICTION 

This Policy, as well as your access to the Website, is subject to and governed by the laws of the United Arab Emirates as applied in the Emirate of Dubai without giving effect to conflicts of law principles thereof. Any dispute regarding this Policy or our handling of your Personal Information and General Information shall be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the Courts in Dubai. 

CONTACT US

If you have any queries, complaints or recommendations about this Policy, or if you believe that any Personal Information that we may hold about you is incorrect or incomplete, please contact us at the following address and we will endeavor to respond to you promptly.
